

### Howie Li Carlsbad, Californ ia Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania

(760) 908 - 8763 howiel@andrew.cmu.edu

#### About:

Having grown up with a wide range extracurricular interests, integrating various fields of thinking is deeply engrained in who I am. I am searching for an experience within the field of architecture that reflects my broad field of passions where I can apply my unique set of skills to further push the bounds of how we create and perceive space in both form and function.

## References:

Jose Pertierra-Arrojo

Special Faculty jpertier@andrew.cmu.edu

Manuel Rodriguez

Studio Instructor and Research Asisstant manuelr@andrew.cmu.edu

#### Education

Carniegie Mellon University (B.Arch 24)
[3.7 GPA]
Pacific Ridge School ('19)
[3.9 GPA]

## **Architectural Experience**

UCLA TeenArch Plus Program (Summer 2017) Carnegie Mellon University First Year Studio (2019 - 2020) Carnegie Mellon University Second Year Studio (Present)

# Teaching Experience

Drawing Teaching Assistant (2020-Present)

Taught by: Professor Douglas Cooper

Design Fabrication Teaching Asistant (2021-Present)

Taught by: Professor Jose Pertierra-Arrojo

#### **Skills**

Analog:

Woodworking Blacksmithing Modeling

Stitching and Embroidering

Drawing Painting Drafting

Digital:

Rhinoceros 7 VRay AutoCAD TwinMotion Procreate Adobe Suite Microsoft Office

Languages:

English Mandarin